



01138435866



burgsebastian94@gmail.com



in/burgossebastian



burgossebastian.com

Computer Skills

Programming

- HTML
- JavaScript
- CSS
- React
- PHP
- Node.js
- Jquery
- Git

3D Design

- 3D Max
- Rhinoceros
- Maya
- Zbrush

2D Design

- PhotoshopAutocad
- Ilustrator
- CorelDraw

Video Editing

- After Effects
- Camtasia Studio
- Adobe Premiere Pro

Languages

Spanish: Native

English: Advance/Profesional

Sebastian Exequiel Burgos

Developer & Designer

About me

Developer and Designer, passionate about computing and technology in constant search to increase my knowledge in any computer field with great facility to learn new tools. Professionally I have 2 years of experience as a Developer and more than 5 years of experience as an Industrial designer. Besides i have complete studies in 3D Design and animation for cinema, including advanced knowledge in various graphic design and multimedia editing softwares.

Experience

Freelance Developer 2022-2023

Complete Web development (html, css, javascript, React)

Development React app (Components, hooks, Redux)

Object oriented programming

Developer Delcapack 2021-2022

Delcapack s.a.

Programming plc delta & ISPSoft 3.07

Front End Developer

Industrial Designer 2016-2022

Delcapack s.a.

Design and development of machinery and dies

Cnc Design programming and operation

Maintenance of company computer equipment

Computer technician 2012-2015

Cpufix s.a.

Software and driver conflict resolution

Installation of operating systems and software packages

Education

Front End Developer

CodeCamp 2021

Html, css , JavaScript, Node.js & React

Php, Jquery, Sass, Bootstrap, Git

Object Oriented Programming

3D Modeling & Animation

Image Campus 2012-2016

3D/2D Design

Multimedia Editing, render y vfx

Bachiller Completed

Institute Don Bosco 2011

Economics and Accounting